<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on Lloyd Tripp</title><link>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on Lloyd Tripp</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 13:49:06 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ChatGPT Needs Prompt Engineering</title><link>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/real_estate_llms/prompt_engineering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 13:49:06 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/real_estate_llms/prompt_engineering/</guid><description>A good response requires a good prompt The term &amp;ldquo;Prompt Engineer&amp;rdquo; is starting to pop up as a person that crafts prompts for ChatGPT and other AI assistants. &amp;ldquo;But wait a minute,&amp;rdquo; you say, &amp;ldquo;wasn&amp;rsquo;t the AI assistant supposed to make it easy for everyone to take advantage of its superior language capabilities?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Now I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to engineer prompts?&amp;rdquo; Well, yes and no. There are two basic approaches that I have used to get the AI assistant to generate the desired response: 1.</description></item><item><title>ChatGPT and Real Estate: A Self-assessment</title><link>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/real_estate_llms/chatgpt_introspection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 17:36:34 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/real_estate_llms/chatgpt_introspection/</guid><description>Self-assessment Before I begin to experiment with engineering prompts for specific tasks, let&amp;rsquo;s have ChatGPT perform a self-assessment of its capabilities in the areas of Real Estate Analytics, Mortgages, and helping Real Estate Agents. After all, a good performance assessment of a human team member begins with a self-assessment.
I think the response is pretty compelling, but we need to verify its capabilities with specifically engineered prompts and chat sessions.</description></item><item><title>ChatGPT for Real Estate: Can't live with it. Can't live without it.</title><link>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/real_estate_llms/chatgpt_and_real_estate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 10:52:39 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/real_estate_llms/chatgpt_and_real_estate/</guid><description>Focus on real estate and finance OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT requires no introduction. A surge of activity has occurred in technical forums, mainstream news sites, and social media platforms. Rather than repeating the broad capabilities of ChatGPT, let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at how AI tools such as ChatGPT may be utilized for Real Estate Analytics, Mortgages, and helping Real Estate Agents. Why real estate and finance? These are huge industries that impact the daily lives of just about everyone and often require a personal touch.</description></item><item><title>ChatGPT is improving scammers' text messages</title><link>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/scammer/scammer_text/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 19:16:09 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/scammer/scammer_text/</guid><description>Improving scammers&amp;rsquo; text messages As with many powerful tools, ChatGPT can be used for illicit purposes. In this case, ChatGPT can be used to correct grammar, punctuation and misspellings in a scammer&amp;rsquo;s text message and rephrase it to read as if it came from a legitimate source. As we have been taught, poor grammar, punctuation and misspellings are often clues that a text message did not come from a legitimate source.</description></item><item><title>Head of Investment Banking Emirates Investment Bank?!?!</title><link>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/scammer/scammer_email/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 18:17:09 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/scammer/scammer_email/</guid><description>More than just improving language ChatGPT can also enable scammers to create emails that seem more genuine and trustworthy. Again, it is not that difficult to spot that it is a scam, but improving the language used in a scam email is just one of the ways Large Language Models (LLMs) can assist scammers. The human-like responses and the ability to understand context means that bots powered by LLMs can carry on a conversation over several text or email exchanges which can build trust before the infected doc or link is sent.</description></item><item><title>ChatGPT vs Bing: Rewrite scam text</title><link>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/scammer/chatgpt_vs_bing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 10:56:37 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/scammer/chatgpt_vs_bing/</guid><description>Who does it better? Microsoft has a preview version of Bing that just got a lot smarter with its own version of ChatGPT. Now you can chat with Bing and get answers in natural language. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare how Bing and OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT performed when revising a scammer&amp;rsquo;s text.
Both revisions are much better than the original, but I prefer the ChatGPT revision; it uses a friendlier tone.
This is an actual text message (without the link):</description></item><item><title>Bold world of opportunities and challenges</title><link>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/pinned/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 13:05:49 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://MrLRTripp.github.io/article/pinned/</guid><description>Renewed public interest in AI Ever since OpenAI made ChatGPT and DALL-E 2 available to the public in late 2022, there has been a renewed interest in Artificial Intelligence.
ChatGPT is a text generator that can converse with humans on various topics, using natural language and common sense. It is based on GPT-3, one of the largest and most powerful language models ever created. ChatGPT can answer questions, tell jokes, write stories, and even generate code or lyrics.</description></item></channel></rss>